You would not believe  what just happened to me.
你肯定不会相信 刚刚在我身上发生了什么事
Wendy! Are you all right?
Wendy! 你没事吧?
Picture this, OK?
想象一下这个, OK?
I'm on my way to work.
我在去上班的路上.
I'm waiting in the subway.
正在等地铁.
The train pulls in, the doors open.
列车开过来了, 门打开了.
But it's packed. People can't get in.
但非常拥挤. 人们进不去.
I see a little space.
我看到一点点空隙.
So I swing my bag in front of me,
So 我把我的包放在我的前面,
to get on the train.
为了上车.
And the doors shut! On the straps!
突然门关上了! 夹住了包的带子!
Bam! And they don't open.
Bam! 它们不开了!
Oh no.
The people right inside the car see this,
车厢里的人们看到了这个,
and start to shout at the conductor.
并且开始大声叫列车员.
He doesn't hear them.
他没有听到这些.
Meanwhile,
同时,
I'm beating on the door and shouting.
我拼命敲门和叫喊.
The train leaves.
列车开走了.
You're joking.
你在开玩笑.
The train leaves,
列车开走了,
and takes my pocketbook with it.
还带走了我的钱包.
There it goes. Down the track.
就那么走了. 沿着轨道.
Unbelievable.
难以置信.
Well, then what happened?
Well, 后来发生了什么?
Thank goodness,
谢天谢地,
someone turned my bag in  at the Lost and Found.
有人返还了我的包 在失物招领处.
Do you believe it?
你相信吗?
Mugged by a train!
被列车抢劫了!
That's city life for you.
那就是你的城市生活.